I don't even understand y'all anymore.
Folks are mad about a video that I made before Zora Mamdani won.
The same way that folks were mad about a video that I talked about Kamala Harrison a year before she was running for office.
Think about this.
Y'all are mad about a video I made before Zora Mamdani won saying that I need to allow people to celebrate.
I made the video before he won.
So are you bots or are you dumb?
Which one is it?
Are you bots or are you dumb?
Because it don't make no sense.
I made a video.
Not even made a video.
I was interviewed a year before Kamala Harris was nominated.
She wasn't nominated, actually.
A year before Kamala Harris became the Democratic nominee for president, where I was asked about what I think about Kamala Harris.
That video was used a year later to attempt to discredit my challenges of her methodology in her campaign, which was to ignore the left.
And that exactly is what they have said is what caused her to lose.
And here we are.
There's a repeat of this happening right now.
So I don't know if it's bots or is it bots or are you dumb?
Because one thing I'm not going to do is let y'all sit here and tell me that I'm wrong and how dare you, Amanda, and blah, blah, blah about something I'm not doing.
It just always looks like there are powers that be, because that's who controls the algorithm, just sowing discord to try to discredit.
And you either believe them or you don't.
But the way in which y'all love to try to come up with reasons to discredit or dislike me is honestly bizarre or it's bots.
And you're not going to do it.
So let's do it.
Let's do it.